Guide to the Clarence Stein papers, 1905-1983.
Stein, Clarence papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Clarence Stein papers, 1905-1983.
3600
Clarence S. Stein
31.4 cubic ft.
Job files, proposed jobs, writings and speeches, general files, research materials, reports, reprints, articles, photographs, medals, certificates, and pins.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Contains job files relating to Clarence Stein's work as an architect and city planner, along with writings, including material pertaining to his book, Toward New Towns for America. Also contains personal and professional correspondence; correspondence and photographs pertaining to travels in China and the Far East; photographs of Stein, friends, and family; and medals, certificates, and pins.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Architect, city planner (lived 1882-1975).
Clarence S. Stein began his career as an architect, but turned his attention to planning by the early 1920s. From 1923 to 1926 he was chairman of the New York State Housing and Regional Planning Commission and was among the founders of the Regional Plan Association in 1923. With his partner Henry Wright, he was a leading proponent of the "garden city" concept of planning. He designed or participated in the design of Sunnyside Gardens, Queens, New York; Radburn, New Jersey; Greenbelt, Maryland; Greendale, Wisconsin; Greenhills, Ohio; and Baldwin Hills Village, Los Angeles, California. Stein was awarded the Gold Medal of the American Institute of Architects (1956), the Distinguished Service Award of the American Institute of Planners (1958), and the Ebenezer Howard Memorial Medal, honoring the British advocate of garden cities.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes job files, proposed jobs, writings and speeches, general files, research materials, and reprints and articles. Job files record Stein's involvement in the design of public buildings, places of worship, museums, and homes; his time as secretary of the Housing Committee of the New York State Reconstruction Commission under Governor Alfred W. Smith; and material on Radburn, New Jersey; Kitimat, British Columbia; Sunnyside Gardens, New York; Hillside Homes, Bronx, New York; and Chatham Village, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. Proposed job files include plans and designs for jobs which never materialized. Writings include material related to the publication of his book, Toward New Towns for America, including photographs, plans, and maps used in the book. Also includes copies of articles and speeches by Stein. General files include unpublished writings; reports on greenbelt towns; material on the Regional Plan Association of America and its successor, the Regional Development Council of America; and community planning and cost studies. Correspondence files include personal and professional correspondence with other planners, including correspondence with the American Institute of Architects (AIA), especially Carl Feiss of that organization; Canadian planners working on Metropolitan Toronto; English planners; personal friends such as Benton MacKaye, Albert Mayer, and Lewis Mumford; and his wife, Aline MacMahon Stein.
Also, correspondence and photographs pertaining to travels in China and the Far East. Reprints and articles include writings of other planners including Frederick Ackerman, Catherine Bauer Wurster, Russell Van Nest Black, Henry Churchill, Vernone De Mars, Arthur Glickson, Eugene Klaber, Benton MacKaye, Albert Mayer, Lewis Mumford, and Henry Wright. Collection also includes photographs and negatives, slides, plans, and maps of much of Stein's major work; and material concerning the work of Marjorie Sewell Cautley (Cornell University Class of 1917), landscape architect for Stein's projects at Radburn, New Jersey and Hillside Homes in the Bronx, New York. Photographs of Stein, friends, and family, and candid and publicity photographs of Aline MacMahon Stein. Medals, certificates, and pins, including Stein's gold medal from the American Institute of Architects, are also included.
Also, a videotape of "Baldwin Hills Village: 'A Village in a City,' " 1942-1950, by Reginald D. Johnson, copied from the 16mm color original film (28 min.).
Plaques and phonograph recordings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Stein, Clarence S.; Ackerman, Frederick.; Black, Russell Van Nest, 1893-1969.; Cautley, Marjorie Sewell, b. 1891.; Churchill, Henry S.(Henry Stern); De Mars, Vernone.; Feiss, Carl.; Glickson, Arthur.; Klaber, Eugene Henry.; MacKaye, Benton, 1879-1975.; Mayer, Albert.; Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990.; Sewell, Marjorie, 1891-; Stein, Aline MacMahon.; Stein, Clarence S.; Wright, Henry, d. 1936.; Wurster, Catherine Bauer.; American Institute of Architects.; New York (State). Reconstruction Commission. Housing Committee.; New York (State). Housing and Regional Planning Commission.; Regional Development Council of America.; Regional Plan Association of America.
Subjects:
Architecture.; City planning.; City planning--California--Los Angeles.; City planning--Pennsylvania--Pittsburgh.; City planning--Maryland--Greenbelt.; City planning--Wisconsin--Greendale.; City planning--Ohio--Greenhills.; City planning--New York (N.Y.)--Bronx.; City planning--British Columbia--Kitimat.; City planning--New Jersey--Radburn.; City planning--New York (N.Y.)--Queens.; Housing.
Places:
Baldwin Hills Village (Los Angeles, Calif.); Chatham Village (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Greenbelt (Md.); Greendale (Wis.); Greenhills (Ohio); Hillside Homes (Bronx, New York, N.Y.); Kitimat (B.C.); Radburn (N.J.); Sunnyside Gardens (Queens, New York, N.Y.); China--Description and travel.; East Asia--Description and travel.
Form and Genre Terms:
Maps.; Negatives (photographic).; Photographs.; Color slides.; Speeches.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Link to an additional partial finding aid. 4 MB PDF file. This file contains the information contained here, but also some additional notes.
Not all the material in the collection is covered by this guide.
RELATED MATERIALS
For some films of Radburn and Sunnyside, see the Marjorie Sewell Cautley papers, #4908, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMM04908.
See also the Milton Glass Kitimat files, #6896, http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMM06896
SERIES LIST
Series I. Biographical and Collection Arrangement Information
Series II. Job File
Series III. Writings and Speeches
Series IV. General File
Series V. Research File
Series VI. Correspondence Files
Series VII. Photographs
Series VIII. Reprints and Articles of Other Professional Planners
Series IX. Sketches, Drawings, Plans and Maps
Series X. Diaries, Journals, Albums, bills, passport, W. W. I. records, 1897-1972
Series XI. Published Material, Books
Series XII. Certificates, pamphlets, projects and postcards
Series XIII. Oversized items
Series XIV. Phonographs and other Media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Biographical and Collection Arrangement Information
  - Biographical information; indexes, lists and correspondence describing collection contents, arrangement and provenance, ca. 1931-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1a and 1b)
    Significant names:
    Cloyd Herbert Finch
    Types of material:
    indexes, lists, correspondence, notes, speeches
- Series II. Job Files
  - Job file, 1918
    - Panama-California Exposition, 1911-1918 and 1961; Balboa Park, San Diego Fair, 1915, 1957, 1961, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Samuel Wood Hamill
      clippings, drafts, correspondence
    - Tyrone, New Mexico, 1918, 1916-1918, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      Subject keywords:
      housing, social work
      Frederick Gutheim
      clippings; articles, memos, blueprints, photographs, correspondence
    - Plans, ca. 1920 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      proposed housing development for the Bendix Aviation Corporation, South Bend, Indiana; Sunnyside; Fort Sheridan Gardens
      Robert D. Kohn
      plans
  - Job File, 1921
    - White Plains Meeting House, 1921 Job File, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      correspondence
  - Job File, 1922
    - Residence: Paiul A. Rie, 1922 (with Ernest Grunsfeld), 1922 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      plan, cross reference
  - Job File, 1923
    - Spuyten Duyvil Housing Development, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      maps, plans
  - Job File, 1924
    - Sunnyside and Radburn; Unit Studies, Room Sizes, 1924, 1930, 1933, 1935, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      Organizations:
      City Housing Corp.
      blueprints, plans
    - Sunnyside (City Housing Corporation), 1924, 1924-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      general plan, house units, organization
      Charles S. Ascher
      Dates:
      1924, 1927, 1947, 1949, 1961, 1964, 1973, 1974
      correspondence, clippings, memos, notes
    - Sunnyside, Queens, 1924, 1924-1932, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
      costs, deed restrictions
      pamphlets and promotional material, articles
    - N.Y. State Commission of Housing and Regional Planning, 1926, 1920-1925, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      articles, reports, references, news releases, notes and charts
    - N.Y. State Commission of Housing and Regional Planning, 1926, 1924-1926, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      pollution abatement, local zoning and planning
      Commission of Housing and Regional Planning
      annual report, reports
    - N.Y. State Commission of Housing and Regional Planning, 1926, ca. 1925 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      natural features and economic development
      maps, charts
    - N.Y. State Commission of Housing and Regional Planning, 1920, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      tax exemption, housing conditions, land value and population
      C.S. Stein, Gov. Alfred E. Smith
      reports, legislative documents, maps in one bound volume
  - Job File, 1927
    - California Institute of Technology, 1927, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      Hardie Phillips
      correspondence, notes, memos
    - C.I.O.T, Chemistry Annex, 1925-1927 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      plans for new Cal Tech buildings [California Institute of Technology]
      photographs, plans
  - Job File, 1927
    - Lavanburg, 1927, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      rehousing the slum dweller
      Beatrice Guenfield Rosahn
      Correspondents:
      National Municipal League
      article
  - Job File, 1929
    - Application of Sunnyside Planning...H.W. (Radburn Superblock Emerging), 1924 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      plans, drawings
    - Radburn plans, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Radburn, 1928, 1930, 1933, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      data, newtown, cost of land, town plan, houses, garden city, mortgage strike at Sunnyside
      Henry Wright, Ralph Eberlain, A.M. Bing
      City Housing Corporation
      notes, memos, outlines
    - [Untitled] Radburn, 1930-1973, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      Radburn idea, town plan
      Charle S. Ascher,Isobel Willcox, Geddes Smith, Tracy Auger
      Date:
      1930-1931, 1953, 1965, 1967-1970, 1973, undated
      articles, clippings, correspondence, map, plopi
    - [Untitled] Radburn, 1930, 1947, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      Radburn critique, budget, garden homes
      pamphlet, memo, manuscript draft
    - L. Blackham: Copies Radburn, 1947-1948, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
      character of the town, education,children
      Louise Blackham
      memos, notes, drafts
    - Radbum, 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      block planning, open spaces
      drafts, revisions, bibliography
    - Radbum, 1947, undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
      garden cities in America, prelude to Radburn and Sunnyside, community plan, intellectual]; climate
      lists, memos, drafts, outlines
    - Radbum, 1948, 1958, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
      material for Greenbelt Book: Radburn idea, garden cities, superblock planning
      notes, correspondence, manuscript drafts
    - Radburn, texts by C.S. Stein, 1948, 1969, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Radburn idea, safety and children at Radburn
      article, correspondence, paper
    - [Untitled] Radburn, 1929-1951 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      liquidation plans, protective restrictions and community administration
      Radburn Management Corporation
      correspondence, notices, pamphlets
    - Radburn Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1930-1965 (Box 1, Folder 29)
      saving housing costs, annual report
      Lesley Ayres
      1930,1947-1948, 1950, 1952, 1965
      The Encyclopedia of Housing, Radburn Management Corporation
      correspondence, articles, memos
    - Radburn Revisited (Reprinted from Herald Tribune, Regional Planning News, 1964), ca. 1952, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      Radburn, Staten Island
      articles
    - Radbum-Fairlawn Thesis: A. P. Van Huyck, 1960-1961,1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      Alfred P. Van Huyck (Director, Urban Renewal, Community Planning Association, Inc. )
      correspondence, clippings, outline, notes
    - Radburn, Photographs, 1934, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 32)
      articles, correspondence
    - Radburn, Airviews, 1929-1967, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
      Regional Plan Association
      1929-1930, 1940, 1967, undated
      photographs, correspondence
  - Job File, 1930
    - Temple Emanu-El with photographs, 1927-1931 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      descriptions
      Charles Butler
      speech notes, reprints, photographs
  - Job File, 1930
    - Hudson Guild Farm, 1930, Andover, N.J. from Architecture, February 1931 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      n.d.e. c-rf
  - Job File, 1931
    - Phipps Houses, 1931-1936, 1935-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      proposed housing development
      Alexander M. Bing, Robert D. Kohn
      1935-1938, 1940, 1945-1946, 1968
      Citizen's Housing and Planning Council of New York, Inc.
      correspondence, plans, memos
    - Phipps, 1932-1940 (Box 1, Folder 37)
      comparative costs
      Ernest Scofield
      memos, correspondence, reprint
  - Job File, 1932
    - Fieldston School, 1932, Pictures and Plans, Architectural Record, 1932, 1931-1932, 1966-1967, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
      Robert D. Kohn (co-architect)
      Ethical Culture Schools of New York City
      articles, map, photographs, correspondence, c-rf
  - CSS-- JOBS, 1932
    - Chatham Village, The Buhl Foundation, also see Towards New Towns, 1931-1961 (Box 1, Folder 39)
      promotional material
      Charles F. Lewis (BF), Charles B. Nutting, (Dir. BF)
      1931-1932, 1935, 1950-1953, 1955-1958, 1960-1961
      The Buhl Foundation, ACTION, Inc., "Chatham'' Village News"
      articles, correspondence, reports, drafts, memos, pamphlets
    - Chatham Village, Buhl Foundation, Charles F. Lewis, 1935-1963, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
      Roy Lubove
      1935-1936, 1949, 1963, undated
      correspondence, photographs, plans, maps, newsletter
  - Job File, 1933
    - Surveys for Secaucus, Milwaukee, Pittsburgh, Los Angeles, San Francisco, 1933, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      proposed housing developments
      Catharine Bauer, Margaret Stein
      reports, correspondence
  - Job File, 1935
    - Wichita Art Institute, 1935, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
      photographs, postcards, c-rf
    - Wichita Art Institute, 1933, "A New ;. Craftsmanship in Cast Stone," Architecture, November 1935, 1929, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - JOBS, 1935: HILLSIDE HOMES
    - Evolution of Four-Room Apt.: Phipps and Hillside, 1926-1935 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      notes, plans, clipping, drawing
    - Hillside: CSS Speech at dedication, June 1935 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      speech
    - "Hillsside Housing" American Architecture, February 1936, illustrated article by CSS, 1934-1936, 1957, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      pamphlet, correspondence, outline
    - "Community Equipment For Hillside House Development", 1935 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      nursery schools, playgrounds
      report, including plans, memos
  - JOB, 1935, HILLSIDE HOMES
    - Hillside, 1936-1960 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      community services, playgrounds
      Albert. Mayer, Louise P. Blackham
      1936, 1949-1950, 1958, 1960
      articles, memos
  - JOBS
    - Maintenance and Operating Costs, F.H.A. Projects including Hillside, ca. 1936, 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      charts, correspondence, memos
    - [Untitled] Pamphlets, 1939, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      healthful housing, construction cost analysis
      American Public Health Association, Committee on the Hygiene of Housing, New York City Housing Authority
      pamphlets
    - "Life in the Community of Hillside, Notes by Louise Blackham, December 19, 1947-January 1948, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      report, notes, memo
    - H3--Hillside -- Photographs and Plans (including Hillside from the air), 1932, 1935, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
      photographs, plans, maps
    - Blueprint for Hillside, block 3, April 14, 1934 (Folder 24)
      Typical floor plan (1st to 4th floor) Heating and electric.
  - Job File, 1935. G-l Resettlement Administration Report, CSS 1935, interleaved with Greenbelt Towns Data
    - "Life In the Communities of Sunnyside,: Radburn, Hillside, Greenbelt, Greenhills" Notes by Louise Blackham, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      community organization, education, child care, character, health, religion, culture
      reports with notes
  - JOBS, Resettlement Administration Report, CSS, 1935, interleaved with Greenbelt Towns Data
    - Greenbelt, 1947-1948, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
      costs, government, education, transportation t O-M of housing, stores, street economy
    - Population and Cost of Government. Greenbelt Towns, undated (Box 2, Folder 15(2))
      report
    - Op -- Maintenance [sic] Gb. gh. gd., government and Housing Management, 1948, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
      cost of local government and community services
      notes
    - Greenbelt, Md., 1947-1960, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
      Leoncird K. Elrahirst
      1947-1950, 1956, 1960, undated
      American Institute of Planners, Agricultural Research Center at Beltsville, Maryland
      legislative bill, correspondence, map, newsletter, drafts, notes
  - JOBS, 1935, Greenbelt, Maryland
    - [Untitled] Greenbelt, 1967-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
      Greenbelt towns
      Resettlement Administration
      newsletter, correspondence, pamphlet, articles
    - Greendale, Wisconsin, 1935, 1935, 1944-1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      community profile
      Walter E. Kroenig, John S. Langill
    - Greendale, Wisconsin, 1935, 1947-1961 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      maintenance and operating costs, liquidation sale
      Walter Kroenig
      1947-1948, 1952, 1956, 1961
      clipping, memo, announcement, outlines
    - Greendale, 1948-1949, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      Elbert Peets
      photographs, correspondence, article
    - Greenhills, Ohio, 1935, 1935, 1944-1948, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
      Louise Blackhara, John S. Langill, Lawrence Tucker
      report, including notes, correspondence, clippings
  - JOBS
    - Los Angeles County Housing A., Harbor Hills, Palos Verdes, Letters of Dozier, Melville, 1938, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 22)
      Melville Jr. (Exec. Director, HA of C of LA), Ralph Eberlain, Reginald D. Johnson
      Housing Authority of the County of Los Angeles
      map, correspondence, press releases, notes, memos
  - Job File, 1939
    - Carmelitos Housing, 1939, Long Beach, Calif., 1926, 1938-1942 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      Harry Cheney, Jacob Crane, Melville Dozier, Elbert Peets, Cecil Schilling (Arch. Ass'd)
      photographs, memos, correspondence, blueprints
  - Job File, 1939
    - Temple of Religion, 1939, World's Fair (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Job File, 1940-1950
    - Contracts: Ascoli, Clairton, Indian Head, Maryland, 1940-1950 and Partnership Agreement, Pine Gardens Housing, Lake Charles, La., Shaler and Stowe, Thousand Gardens (Baldwin Hills Village), 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      Ralph Eberlin
      National Housing Agency
      contracts, correspondence, maps, articles
  - Job File, 1941
    - Baldwin Hills Village, 1941, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      application for mortgage insurance
      plans, memos
  - Job File
    - Baldwin Hills Village, 1941, 1938-1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      funding, construction outlines, community life, operating expenses
      Robert Alexander, Lewis Wilson, Reginald Johnson
      1938, 1940, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1951, 1960, 1966
      correspondence, memos, notes
    - Baldwin Hills Village, 1941, 1939-1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
      promotional material, dam breakage
      1939, 1944, 1959, 1963, 1966, undated
      pamphlets, clippings, reprints, map
  - Job File
    - Harbor Hills Housing, 1941, Pencil Pointe, November 1941 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      1939, 1941
      plan, article, draft, photo
  - Job File
    - Clairton, Pa., Job, 1941, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
      defense housing project
      photo, picture
  - Job File, 1941
    - Shaler Township, Pa., 1941, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
      picture, plans
    - Comparative Cost of Hillside Type Houses as Developed for Shaler and Stowe and ordinary Type Houses, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 32)
      drawings, memo, plans, correspondence
  - Job File, 1941
    - Stowe Township, Pa., 1941, Defense Housing Project, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 33)
      photographs, blueprints, plans
    - Indian Head, Maryland, 1941, Defense Housing Project, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
      parking area
      blueprint, plan
  - Job File, 1954
    - Chandigarrh: Job File, 1950, 1947-1954, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
      neighborhood center design requirements, Radburn idea, public buildings, superblocks
      Albert Mayer
      Mayer and Whittlesey
      memos, correspondence, articles
  - Job File, 1950, Stevenage Town Center, 1950, English New Town
    - Stevenage Town Center. Early Phase (Box 2, Folder 36)
      community center
      Clifford Holliday (SDC), Gordon Stephenson
      Stevenage Development Corporation
      articles, correspondence, memo, outline, drawings
    - Stevenage Town Center (Box 2, Folder 37)
      English new town
      photographs, articles, plans, maps
  - Job File, 1951
    - Contracts -- CSS and Alcan b J.B. White, Eric West, 1951-1953 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      Aluminum Company of Canada, Limited
      correspondence, vouchers
    - Kitimat Proposal, Method of Work, 1951, 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      recruitment of Stein, agreement, cost estimates and tentative job description
      Eric West, A.W. Whitaker, Jr.
      correspondence, memo, notes
    - Aluminium Co. of Canada, Inc., 1951-1952 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      planning objectives for Kitimat, contract
      Julian Whittlesey, Roger Willcox
      memos, draft/correspondence
    - Kitimat, CSS, Notes etc. (Box 2, Folder 41)
      development and problems
      J.B. White, Hugh Pomeroy
      notes, clipping, pamphlet, correspondence
  - Job File
    - Kitimat, 1952, Roger Willcox (Box 2, Folder 42)
      Dana Bartholomew, J.S. Shakespeare
      correspondence, notes, memo
  - Job File
    - Aluminum Co., 1951-1958 (Box 2, Folder 43)
      Kitimat-related correspondence and notes
      James E. Dudley, Eric F. West, R. M. Hopkins, Julian Whittlesey
    - "Six Months Progress Report for Kitimat Townsite Planning March 7, 1952", 1952 (Box 2, Folder 44)
      R.E. Powell, Pres., Alcan; Roger Willcox
    - Kitimat Part I, Kitimat Part II, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 45)
      planning activities, incorporation, budget, publicity, organization, education and health
      Roger Willcox, C.M. Henderson
      reports, including maps, correspondence, memos
    - A Study of Commercial Requirements for Stage I, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Larry Smith and Company
    - Commerical Aspects of Kitimat, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Kitimat Townsite Report, Sections 1-7, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      reference material and reports
    - Kitimat Townsite Report, Sections 8-32, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      reference materials, reports
    - Sixth Set of supplementary pages for Kitimat Townsite Report, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Roger Willcox
      reports, addendums